Finding Aid for the James G. Stahlman Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
James G. Stahlman Papers
multiple
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0413
55.86 linear_feet
- Newspaper Career - Correspondence
  - Outgoing, May 8, 1918 (Box IV-1, Folder 1)
  - Outgoing, Sep. 24, 25, 1930 (Box IV-1, Folder 2)
  - Outgoing, Sep. 26, 1930 (Box IV-1, Folder 3)
  - Outgoing, Sep. 29, 30, 1930 (Box IV-1, Folder 4)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 2 - Dec. 15, 1930 (Box IV-1, Folder 5)
  - Outgoing, Jul. 4 - Apr. 18, 1932 (Box IV-1, Folder 6)
  - Outgoing, May 9 - Jul. 25, 1932 (Box IV-1, Folder 7)
  - Outgoing, Jul. 25, 1932 (Box IV-1, Folder 8)
  - Outgoing, Jul. 26, 1932 (Box IV-1, Folder 9)
  - Outgoing, Jul. 26 - 30, 1932 (Box IV-1, Folder 10)
  - Outgoing, Aug. 1 - Sep. 22, 1932 (Box IV-1, Folder 11)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 26 - Dec. 29, 1932, undated (1932) (Box IV-1, Folder 12)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 3 - 9, 1933 (Box IV-1, Folder 13)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 11 - 23, 1933 (Box IV-1, Folder 14)
  - Outgoing, Feb. 4 - 28, 1933 (Box IV-1, Folder 15)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 1 - 27, 1933 (Box IV-1, Folder 16)
  - Outgoing, Apr. 11 - May 9, 1933 (Box IV-1, Folder 17)
  - Outgoing, May 10 - 17, 1933 (Box IV-1, Folder 18)
  - Outgoing, May 18 - 25, 1933 (Box IV-1, Folder 19)
  - Outgoing, May 26 - Jun. 3, 1933 (Box IV-1, Folder 20)
  - Outgoing, Jun. 10 - 19, 1933 (Box IV-1, Folder 21)
  - Outgoing, Jun. 20 - Jul. 8, 1933 (Box IV-1, Folder 22)
  - Outgoing, Jul. 10 - Aug. 29, 1933 (Box IV-1, Folder 23)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 5 1933 - Apr. 1934 (Box IV-1, Folder 24)
  - Outgoing, May 18 - Sep. 29, 1934 (Box IV-1, Folder 25)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 1 - 10, 1934 (Box IV-1, Folder 26)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 11 - Nov. 6, 1934 (Box IV-1, Folder 27)
  - Outgoing, Nov. 10 - Dec. 11, 1934 (Box IV-1, Folder 28)
  - Outgoing, Dec. 12 - 31, 1934, undated (1934) (Box IV-1, Folder 29)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 1 - 29, 1935 (Box IV-1, Folder 30)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 30 - Feb. 2, 1935 (Box IV-1, Folder 31)
  - Outgoing, Feb. 5 - 14, 1935 (Box IV-2, Folder 1)
  - Outgoing, Feb. 15 - 16, 1935 (Box IV-2, Folder 2)
  - Outgoing, Feb. 18 -19, 1935 (Box IV-2, Folder 3)
  - Outgoing, Feb. 20 - 27, 1935 (Box IV-2, Folder 4)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 1 - 30, 1935 (Box IV-2, Folder 5)
  - Outgoing, Apr. 1 - May 4, 1935 (Box IV-2, Folder 6)
  - Outgoing, May 6 - 8, 1935 (Box IV-2, Folder 7)
  - Outgoing, May 10 - 31, 1935 (Box IV-2, Folder 8)
  - Outgoing, Jun. 1 - 7, 1935 (Box IV-2, Folder 9)
  - Outgoing, Jun. 8 - 19, 1935 (Box IV-2, Folder 10)
  - Outgoing, Aug. 2 - 17, 1935 (Box IV-2, Folder 11)
  - Outgoing, Aug. 19 - Sep. 6, 1935 (Box IV-2, Folder 12)
  - Outgoing, Sep. 7 - Oct. 26, 1935 (Box IV-2, Folder 13)
  - Outgoing, Nov. 1 - 23, 1935 (Box IV-2, Folder 14)
  - Outgoing, Dec. 7, 1935 - Feb. 5, 1936 (Box IV-2, Folder 15)
  - Outgoing, Feb. 6 - Mar. 25, 1936 (Box IV-2, Folder 16)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 27 - Apr. 29, 1936 (Box IV-2, Folder 17)
  - Outgoing, Apr. 30 - May 30, 1936 (Box IV-2, Folder 18)
  - Outgoing, Jun. 1 - Jul. 7, 1936 (Box IV-2, Folder 19)
  - Outgoing, Jul. 10 - Aug. 11, 1936 (Box IV-2, Folder 20)
  - Outgoing, Aug. 12 - 29, 1936 (Box IV-2, Folder 21)
  - Outgoing, Sep. 2 - 14, 1936 (Box IV-2, Folder 22)
  - Outgoing, Sep. 15 - Nov. 12, 1936, undated (1936) (Box IV-2, Folder 23)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 7 - Feb. 16, 1937 (Box IV-2, Folder 24)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 2-31, 1937 (Box IV-2, Folder 25)
  - Outgoing, Apr. 26 - 28, 1937 (Box IV-2, Folder 26)
  - Outgoing, Apr. 29, 1937 (Box IV-3, Folder 1)
  - Outgoing, Apr. 30, 1937 (Box IV-3, Folder 2)
  - Outgoing, May 1, 1937 (Box IV-3, Folder 3)
  - Outgoing, May 3, 1937 (Box IV-3, Folder 4)
  - Outgoing, May 6 - 7, 1937 (Box IV-3, Folder 5)
  - Outgoing, May 8 - 10, 1937 (Box IV-3, Folder 6)
  - Outgoing, May 11 - 12, 1937 (Box IV-3, Folder 7)
  - Outgoing, May 13 - 14, 1937 (Box IV-3, Folder 8)
  - Outgoing, May 15 - 16, 1937 (Box IV-3, Folder 9)
  - Outgoing, May 19 - 20, 1937 (Box IV-3, Folder 10)
  - Outgoing, May 21 - Jun. 5, 1937 (Box IV-3, Folder 11)
  - Outgoing, Jun. 9 - Jul. 22, 1937 (Box IV-3, Folder 12)
  - Outgoing, Jul. 26 - Aug. 28, 1937 (Box IV-3, Folder 13)
  - Outgoing, Aug. 30 - Sep. 18, 1937 (Box IV-3, Folder 14)
  - Outgoing, Sep. 20 - Oct. 13, 1937 (Box IV-3, Folder 15)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 14 - 29, 1937 (Box IV-3, Folder 16)
  - Outgoing, Nov. 1 - 10, 1937 (Box IV-3, Folder 17)
  - Outgoing, Nov. 11 -30, 1937 (Box IV-3, Folder 18)
  - Outgoing, Dec. 1 - 8, 1937 (Box IV-3, Folder 19)
  - Outgoing, Dec. 18 - 22, 1937 (Box IV-3, Folder 20)
  - Outgoing, Dec. 23 - 30, 1937, undated (1937) (Box IV-3, Folder 21)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 3 - Mar. 30, 1938 (Box IV-3, Folder 22)
  - Outgoing, Apr. 2 - May 4, 1938 (Box IV-3, Folder 23)
  - Outgoing, May 5 - Sep. 9, 1938 (Box IV-3, Folder 24)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 17 - Nov. 30, 1938 (Box IV-3, Folder 25)
  - Outgoing, Dec. 2-31, 1938 (Box IV-3, Folder 26)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 4 -31, 1939 (Box IV-3, Folder 27)
  - Outgoing, Feb. 1 - 3, 1939 (Box IV-4, Folder 1)
  - Outgoing, Feb. 6 - 15, 1939 (Box IV-4, Folder 2)
  - Outgoing, Feb. 17 - 18, 1939 (Box IV-4, Folder 3)
  - Outgoing, Feb. 20 - 27, 1939 (Box IV-4, Folder 4)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 1 - 6, 1939 (Box IV-4, Folder 5)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 7 - 13, 1939 (Box IV-4, Folder 6)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 14 - 21, 1939 (Box IV-4, Folder 7)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 22 - 31, 193 9 (Box IV-4, Folder 8)
  - Outgoing, Apr. 1 - 10, 1939 (Box IV-4, Folder 9)
  - Outgoing, Apr. 12 - 14, 1939 (Box IV-4, Folder 10)
  - Outgoing, Apr. 15 -20, 1939 (Box IV-4, Folder 11)
  - Outgoing, May 1, 1939 (Box IV-4, Folder 12)
  - Outgoing, May 2 - 5, 1939 (Box IV-4, Folder 13)
  - Outgoing, May 9 - 12, 1939 (Box IV-4, Folder 14)
  - Outgoing, May 13 - Jun. 7, 1939 (Box IV-4, Folder 15)
  - Outgoing, Jun. 12 - 30, 1939 (Box IV-4, Folder 16)
  - Outgoing, Jul. 5 - 31, 1939 (Box IV-4, Folder 17)
  - Outgoing, Aug. 2 - Sep. 29, 1939 (Box IV-4, Folder 18)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 2 - 27, 1939 (Box IV-4, Folder 19)
  - Outgoing, Nov. 7 - Dec. 21, 1939 (Box IV-4, Folder 20)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 2 - Feb. 24, 1940 (Box IV-4, Folder 21)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 4 - 30, 1940 (Box IV-4, Folder 22)
  - Outgoing, Apr. 3 - May 6, 1940 (Box IV-4, Folder 23)
  - Outgoing, May 8 -Jul. 31, 1940 (Box IV-4, Folder 24)
  - Outgoing, Aug. 2 - Sep. 25, 1940 (Box IV-4, Folder 25)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 8 - Nov. 25, 1940 (Box IV-4, Folder 26)
  - Outgoing, Nov. 26 - Dec. 23, 1940, undated (1940) (Box IV-4, Folder 27)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 5 - Feb. 23, 1941 (Box IV-4, Folder 28)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 1 - Dec. 31, 1941 (Box IV-4, Folder 29)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 1 - Apr. 28, 1942 (Box IV-4, Folder 30)
  - Outgoing, May 11 - Aug. 29, 1942 (Box IV-4, Folder 31)
  - Outgoing, Sep. 4 - Dec. 26, 1942 (Box IV-4, Folder 32)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 4 - Apr. 20, 1943 (Box IV-4, Folder 33)
  - Outgoing, May 3, 1943 - Sep. 11, 1945 (Box IV-5, Folder 1)
  - Outgoing, Sep. 12 - 24, 1945 (Box IV-5, Folder 2)
  - Outgoing, Sep. 25 - Dec. 31, 1945 (Box IV-5, Folder 3)
  - Outgoing, Apr. 3 - 30, 1946 (Box IV-5, Folder 4)
  - Outgoing, May 4, 1946 - Mar. 31, 1947 (Box IV-5, Folder 5)
  - Outgoing, Apr. 4, 1947 - Oct. 27, 1949 (Box IV-5, Folder 6)
  - Outgoing, Nov. 16, 1949 - Jan. 9, 1950 (Box IV-5, Folder 7)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 10 - 24, 1950 (Box IV-5, Folder 8)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 25 - Feb. 21, 1950 (Box IV-5, Folder 9)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 9 - May 2, 1950 (Box IV-5, Folder 10)
  - Outgoing, May 4 - 22, 1950 (Box IV-5, Folder 11)
  - Outgoing, Jun. 1 - 23, 1950 (Box IV-5, Folder 12)
  - Outgoing, Jul. 10 - 31, 1950 (Box IV-5, Folder 13)
  - Outgoing, Sep. 7 - 28, 1950 (Box IV-5, Folder 14)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 16 - 31, 1950 (Box IV-5, Folder 15)
  - Outgoing, Nov. 1 - 30, 1950 (Box IV-5, Folder 16)
  - Outgoing, Dec. 1 - 29, 1950 (Box IV-5, Folder 17)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 5 - 30, 1951 (Box IV-5, Folder 18)
  - Outgoing, Feb. 5 - Mar. 30, 1951 (Box IV-5, Folder 19)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 31 - Apr. 3, 1951 (Box IV-5, Folder 20)
  - Outgoing, Apr. 5 - 10, 1951 (Box IV-5, Folder 21)
  - Outgoing, Apr. 11, 1951 (Box IV-5, Folder 22)
  - Outgoing, Apr. 12, 1951 (Box IV-5, Folder 23)
  - Outgoing, Apr. 13 - 30, 1951 (Box IV-5, Folder 24)
  - Outgoing, May 1 - 22, 1951 (Box IV-5, Folder 25)
  - Outgoing, May 23 - 28, 1951 (Box IV-5, Folder 26)
  - Outgoing, Jun. 8 - Sep. 24, 1951 (Box IV-5, Folder 27)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 2 - Nov. 12, 1951 (Box IV-5, Folder 28)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 18 - 28, 1953 (Box IV-6, Folder 1)
  - Outgoing, Feb. 2 - Apr. 27, 1953 (Box IV-6, Folder 2)
  - Outgoing, May 13 - Dec. 7, 1953 (Box IV-6, Folder 3)
  - Outgoing, Dec. 9, 1953 - Feb. 22, 1954 (Box IV-6, Folder 4)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 4 - Apr. 5, 1954 (Box IV-6, Folder 5)
  - Outgoing, Apr. 7 - Jun. 10, 1954 (Box IV-6, Folder 6)
  - Outgoing, Jun. 18 - Jul. 25, 1954 (Box IV-6, Folder 7)
  - Outgoing, Aug. 23 - Nov. 9, 1954 (Box IV-6, Folder 8)
  - Outgoing, Nov. 10 - 11, 1954 (Box IV-6, Folder 9)
  - Outgoing, Nov. 15 - Nov. 19, 1954 (Box IV-6, Folder 10)
  - Outgoing, Nov. 24 - Dec. 31, 1954 (Box IV-6, Folder 11)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 4 - 19, 1955 (Box IV-6, Folder 12)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 24, 1955 (Box IV-6, Folder 13)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 24, 1955 (Box IV-6, Folder 14)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 25 - 26, 1955 (Box IV-6, Folder 15)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 27 - 28, 1955 (Box IV-6, Folder 16)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 30 - 31, 195 5 (Box IV-6, Folder 17)
  - Outgoing, Feb. 1, 1955 (Box IV-6, Folder 18)
  - Outgoing, Feb. 2 - 3, 1955 (Box IV-6, Folder 19)
  - Outgoing, Feb. 4, 1955 (Box IV-7, Folder 1)
  - Outgoing, Feb. 7 - 10, 1955 (Box IV-7, Folder 2)
  - Outgoing, Feb. 11 - 23, 1955 (Box IV-7, Folder 3)
  - Outgoing, Feb. 23 - Mar. 7, 1955 (Box IV-7, Folder 4)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 8 - 9, 1955 (Box IV-7, Folder 5)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 10, 1955 (Box IV-7, Folder 6)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 11, 1955 (Box IV-7, Folder 7)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 12, 1955 (Box IV-7, Folder 8)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 14, 1955 (Box IV-7, Folder 9)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 14, 1955 (Box IV-7, Folder 10)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 15, 1955 (Box IV-7, Folder 11)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 16, 1955 (Box IV-7, Folder 12)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 17 - 18, 1955 (Box IV-7, Folder 13)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 21 - 31, 1955 (Box IV-7, Folder 14)
  - Outgoing, Apr. 1 - 4, 1955 (Box IV-7, Folder 15)
  - Outgoing, Apr. 5 - 30, 1955 (Box IV-7, Folder 16)
  - Outgoing, May 2 - 9, 1955 (Box IV-7, Folder 17)
  - Outgoing, May 10 - 18, 1955 (Box IV-7, Folder 18)
  - Outgoing, May 19 - 31, 1955 (Box IV-7, Folder 19)
  - Outgoing, Jun. 1 - Aug. 31, 1955 (Box IV-7, Folder 20)
  - Outgoing, Sep. 2 - 17, 1955 (Box IV-7, Folder 21)
  - Outgoing, Sep. 19 - 23, 1955 (Box IV-7, Folder 22)
  - Outgoing, Sep. 26 - Oct. 24, 1955 (Box IV-7, Folder 23)
  - Outgoing, Nov. 4 - 8, 1955 (Box IV-7, Folder 24)
  - Outgoing, Nov. 9 - 10, 1955 (Box IV-7, Folder 25)
  - Outgoing, Nov. 11 - 15, 1955 (Box IV-8, Folder 1)
  - Outgoing, Nov. 16 - 23, 1955 (Box IV-8, Folder 2)
  - Outgoing, Nov. 25 - 28, 1955 (Box IV-8, Folder 3)
  - Outgoing, Nov. 29 - Dec. 5, 1955 (Box IV-8, Folder 4)
  - Outgoing, Dec. 6 - 16, 1955 (Box IV-8, Folder 5)
  - Outgoing, Dec. 20 - 30, 1955 (Box IV-8, Folder 6)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 3 - 18, 1956 (Box IV-8, Folder 7)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 19 - 25, 1956 (Box IV-8, Folder 8)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 26 - Feb. 6, 1956 (Box IV-8, Folder 9)
  - Outgoing, Feb. 7 - 10, 1956 (Box IV-8, Folder 10)
  - Outgoing, Feb. 11 - 17, 1956 (Box IV-8, Folder 11)
  - Outgoing, Feb. 18 - 29, 1956 (Box IV-8, Folder 12)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 1 - 16, 1956 (Box IV-8, Folder 13)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 17 - 27, 1956 (Box IV-8, Folder 14)
  - Outgoing, Apr. 9 - May 1, 1956 (Box IV-8, Folder 15)
  - Outgoing, May 2 - 14, 195 6 (Box IV-8, Folder 16)
  - Outgoing, May 18 - 31,1956 (Box IV-8, Folder 17)
  - Outgoing, Jun. 1 - 29, 1956 (Box IV-8, Folder 18)
  - Outgoing, Jul. 3 - 23, 1956 (Box IV-8, Folder 19)
  - Outgoing, Jul. 24 - Aug. 8, 1956 (Box IV-8, Folder 20)
  - Outgoing, Aug. 9 - Sep. 26, 1956 (Box IV-8, Folder 21)
  - Outgoing, Sep. 27 - Oct. 2, 1956 (Box IV-8, Folder 22)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 3 - 10, 1956 (Box IV-8, Folder 23)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 11 - 16, 1956 (Box IV-8, Folder 24)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 17 - 18, 1956 (Box IV-9, Folder 1)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 19 - Nov. 6, 1956 (Box IV-9, Folder 2)
  - Outgoing, Nov. 6, 1956 (Box IV-9, Folder 3)
  - Outgoing, Nov. 7 - 26, 1956 (Box IV-9, Folder 4)
  - Outgoing, Nov. 27, 1956 - Jan. 16, 1957 (Box IV-9, Folder 5)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 22 - Mar. 28, 1957 (Box IV-9, Folder 6)
  - Outgoing, Apr. 8 - Jul. 29, 1957 (Box IV-9, Folder 7)
  - Outgoing, Aug. 8 - Oct. 10, 1957 (Box IV-9, Folder 8)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 21, 1957 - Apr. 28, 1958 (Box IV-9, Folder 9)
  - Outgoing, May 19 - Jul. 31, 1958 (Box IV-9, Folder 10)
  - Outgoing, Aug. 12 - Sep. 29, 1958 (Box IV-9, Folder 11)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 4 - Dec. 1, 1958 (Box IV-9, Folder 12)
  - Outgoing, Dec. 4 - 9, 1958 (Box IV-9, Folder 13)
  - Outgoing, Dec. 15, 1958 - May 7, 1959 (Box IV-9, Folder 14)
  - Outgoing, Aug. 14 - Dec. 28, 1959 (Box IV-9, Folder 15)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 4 - 28, 1960 (Box IV-9, Folder 16)
  - Outgoing, Feb. 9 - Aug. 5, 1960 (Box IV-9, Folder 17)
  - Outgoing, Sep. 7 - Dec. 20, 1960 (Box IV-9, Folder 18)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 11 - Mar. 30, 1961 (Box IV-9, Folder 19)
  - Outgoing, May 25, 1961 - Apr. 3, 1962 (Box IV-9, Folder 20)
  - Outgoing, Jul. 3 - 13, 1962 (Box IV-9, Folder 21)
  - Outgoing, Jul. 16 - 23, 1962 (Box IV-9, Folder 22)
  - Outgoing, Jul. 25 - Oct. 5, 1962 (Box IV-9, Folder 23)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 8, 1962 - Jan. 29, 1963 (Box IV-10, Folder 1)
  - Outgoing, Feb. 4 - Jul. 29, 1963 (Box IV-10, Folder 2)
  - Outgoing, Aug. 5, 1963 - Mar. 18, 1964 (Box IV-10, Folder 3)
  - Outgoing, Apr. 2 - Dec. 15, 1964 (Box IV-10, Folder 4)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 16 - Jul. 30, 1965 (Box IV-10, Folder 5)
  - Outgoing, Aug. 27, 1965 - Jan. 27, 1966 (Box IV-10, Folder 6)
  - Outgoing, Feb. 7 - Aug. 16, 1966 (Box IV-10, Folder 7)
  - Outgoing, Aug. 19 - Oct. 19, 1966 (Box IV-10, Folder 8)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 20 - Dec. 27, 1966 (Box IV-10, Folder 9)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 3 - Aug. 7, 1967 (Box IV-10, Folder 10)
  - Outgoing, Aug. 17 - 21, 1967 (Box IV-10, Folder 11)
  - Outgoing, Aug. 22 - 30, 1967 (Box IV-10, Folder 12)
  - Outgoing, Sep. 1 - Dec. 26, 1967 (Box IV-10, Folder 13)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 22 - Jun. 26, 1968 (Box IV-10, Folder 14)
  - Outgoing, Jul. 5 - Dec. 18, 1968 (Box IV-10, Folder 15)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 6 - Jun. 30, 1969 (Box IV-10, Folder 16)
  - Outgoing, Jul. 2 - Aug. 27, 1969 (Box IV-10, Folder 17)
  - Outgoing, Sep. 10 - Nov. 17, 1969 (Box IV-10, Folder 18)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 29 - Jul. 30, 1970 (Box IV-10, Folder 19)
  - Outgoing, Aug. 3, 1970 - Mar. 30, 1971 (Box IV-10, Folder 20)
  - Outgoing, Apr. 2 - Sep. 27, 1971 (Box IV-10, Folder 21)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 4 - Nov. 18, 1971 (Box IV-10, Folder 22)
  - Outgoing, Dec. 13, 1971 - Jan. 14, 1972 (Box IV-10, Folder 23)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 17, 1972 (Box IV-10, Folder 24)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 18, 1972 (Box IV-10, Folder 25)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 19, 1972 (Box IV-10, Folder 26)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 20, 1972 (Box IV-10, Folder 27)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 21 - 24, 1972 (Box IV-11, Folder 1)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 25 - 28, 1972 (Box IV-11, Folder 2)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 31 - Feb. 9, 1972 (Box IV-11, Folder 3)
  - Outgoing, Feb. 10 - Mar. 20, 1972 (Box IV-11, Folder 4)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 21 - 30, 1972 (Box IV-11, Folder 5)
  - Outgoing, Jun. 6, 1972 (Box IV-11, Folder 6)
  - Outgoing, Jun. 7, 1972 (Box IV-11, Folder 7)
  - Outgoing, Jun. 8, 1972 (Box IV-11, Folder 8)
  - Outgoing, Jun. 12 - 13, 1972 (Box IV-11, Folder 9)
  - Outgoing, Jun. 14 - 19, 1972 (Box IV-11, Folder 10)
  - Outgoing, Jun. 21 - Jul. 8, 1972 (Box IV-11, Folder 11)
  - Outgoing, Jul. 25 - Oct. 30, 1972 (Box IV-11, Folder 12)
  - Outgoing, Nov. 1, 1972 - Jan. 31, 1973 (Box IV-11, Folder 13)
  - Outgoing, Feb. 1 - May 8, 1973 (Box IV-11, Folder 14)
  - Outgoing, May 14 - Jul. 31, 1973 (Box IV-11, Folder 15)
  - Outgoing, Aug. 1 - Sep. 27, 1973 (Box IV-11, Folder 16)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 1 - Dec. 31, 1973 (Box IV-11, Folder 17)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 14 - Aug. 29, 1974 (Box IV-11, Folder 18)
  - Outgoing, Sep. 3 - Dec. 31, 1974 (Box IV-11, Folder 19)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 6 - Apr. 11, 1975 (Box IV-11, Folder 20)
  - Outgoing, May 5 - Nov. 26, 1975 (Box IV-11, Folder 21)
  - Outgoing, Dec. 2, 1975 - Apr. 9, 1976 (Box IV-11, Folder 22)
  - Outgoing, Apr. 12 - 28, 1976; undated (Box IV-11, Folder 23)
  - Incoming, Abernethy - Adams (Box IV-12, Folder 1)
  - Incoming, Adamson - Adler (Box IV-12, Folder 2)
  - Incoming, Adrian - Ahlgren (Box IV-12, Folder 3)
  - Incoming, Aiken - Alexander (Box IV-12, Folder 4)
  - Incoming, Alisky - Amis (Box IV-12, Folder 5)
  - Incoming, American - Americas (Box IV-12, Folder 6)
  - Incoming, Amos - Anderson (Box IV-12, Folder 7)
  - Incoming, Anderson, E. R. (Box IV-12, Folder 8)
  - Incoming, Anderson, P. (Box IV-12, Folder 9)
  - Incoming, Anderson, R - Anderson, W. (Box IV-12, Folder 10)
  - Incoming, Andrews - Appert, D. (Box IV-12, Folder 11)
  - Incoming, Appert, D. (Box IV-12, Folder 12)
  - Incoming, Appleton - Armas (Box IV-12, Folder 13)
  - Incoming, Armistead, C. - Armistead, G. (Box IV-12, Folder 14)
  - Incoming, Armistead, G. (Box IV-12, Folder 15)
  - Incoming, Armistead, G. - Armistead, H. (Box IV-12, Folder 16)
  - Incoming, Armistead, James H. (Box IV-12, Folder 17)
  - Incoming, Armistead, James H. (Box IV-12, Folder 18)
  - Incoming, Armistead, L. - Arnold (Box IV-12, Folder 19)
  - Incoming, Ashworth - Autry (Box IV-12, Folder 20)
  - Incoming, Avent - Azzarello (Box IV-12, Folder 21)
  - Incoming, Bachelder, P. A. (Box IV-12, Folder 22)
  - Incoming, Bachelder, P. A. (Box IV-12, Folder 23)
  - Incoming, Bachelder, P. A. (Box IV-12, Folder 24)
  - Incoming, Bachelder, P. A. - Bailey (Box IV-13, Folder 1)
  - Incoming, Baillie - Baker (Box IV-13, Folder 2)
  - Incoming, Baldwin - Balls (Box IV-13, Folder 3)
  - Incoming, Baltes - Barnard (Box IV-13, Folder 4)
  - Incoming, Barnes, M. (Box IV-13, Folder 5)
  - Incoming, Barnes, O. - Barnum, J. (Box IV-13, Folder 6)
  - Incoming, Barnum, J. (Box IV-13, Folder 7)
  - Incoming, Barr - Bass (Box IV-13, Folder 8)
  - Incoming, Bassett - Battle (Box IV-13, Folder 9)
  - Incoming, Baughman - Baxter, F. (Box IV-13, Folder 10)
  - Incoming, Baxter, J. - Beck (Box IV-13, Folder 11)
  - Incoming, Becker - Beebe (Box IV-13, Folder 12)
  - Incoming, Beeche - Bellington (Box IV-13, Folder 13)
  - Incoming, Beltrain - Bennett (Box IV-13, Folder 14)
  - Incoming, Benson (Box IV-13, Folder 15)
  - Incoming, Benson - Bernet (Box IV-13, Folder 16)
  - Incoming, Bernrieder (Box IV-13, Folder 17)
  - Incoming, Biddle (Box IV-13, Folder 18)
  - Incoming, Biggers (Box IV-13, Folder 19)
  - Incoming, Bingham - Blacklidge (Box IV-13, Folder 20)
  - Incoming, Blake - Blalock (Box IV-13, Folder 21)
  - Incoming, Boden (Box IV-14, Folder 1)
  - Incoming, Bogue - Bootman (Box IV-14, Folder 2)
  - Incoming, Borchert - Bouldin (Box IV-14, Folder 3)
  - Incoming, Boult, R. (Box IV-14, Folder 4)
  - Incoming, Boult, R. (Box IV-14, Folder 5)
  - Incoming, Boult, R. (Box IV-14, Folder 6)
  - Incoming, Bourne - Bowen (Box IV-14, Folder 7)
  - Incoming, Bowers - Brackman (Box IV-14, Folder 8)
  - Incoming, Braden, S. (Box IV-14, Folder 9)
  - Incoming, Bradford - Bradler (Box IV-14, Folder 10)
  - Incoming, Bradshaw - Brandenburg (Box IV-14, Folder 11)
  - Incoming, Brandes - Brattstrom (Box IV-14, Folder 12)
  - Incoming, Braxton, H. Gale (Box IV-14, Folder 13)
  - Incoming, Breen - Brent (Box IV-14, Folder 14)
  - Incoming, Bretsch - Broden (Box IV-14, Folder 15)
  - Incoming, Brogan, J. (Box IV-14, Folder 16)
  - Incoming, Brogan, J. (Box IV-14, Folder 17)
  - Incoming, Bromberg - Brown, C. (Box IV-14, Folder 18)
  - Incoming, Brown, E. - Brown, J. (Box IV-14, Folder 19)
  - Incoming, Brown, L. Brown, R. (Box IV-14, Folder 20)
  - Incoming, Brown, S. - Bryan (Box IV-14, Folder 21)
  - Incoming, Buchanan - Bureau (Box IV-14, Folder 22)
  - Incoming, Burg - Burke (Box IV-15, Folder 1)
  - Incoming, Burkhalter - Bush (Box IV-15, Folder 2)
  - Incoming, Bustamante - Butler (Box IV-15, Folder 3)
  - Incoming, Buzzell - Byrd, H. (Box IV-15, Folder 4)
  - Incoming, Byrd, R. - Caldwell (Box IV-15, Folder 5)
  - Incoming, Calhoun - Campbell (Box IV-15, Folder 6)
  - Incoming, Canel, James (Box IV-15, Folder 7)
  - Incoming, Canel, James (Box IV-15, Folder 8)
  - Incoming, Canel, James (Box IV-15, Folder 9)
  - Incoming, Canel, James (Box IV-15, Folder 10)
  - Incoming, Canel, James (Box IV-15, Folder 11)
  - Incoming, Canel, James (Box IV-15, Folder 12)
  - Incoming, Canel, James (Box IV-15, Folder 13)
  - Incoming, Canel, James (Box IV-15, Folder 14)
  - Incoming, Canel, James (Box IV-15, Folder 15)
  - Incoming, Canel, James, B. (Box IV-15, Folder 16)
  - Incoming, Canel, James, B. (Box IV-15, Folder 17)
  - Incoming, Canel, James, B. (Box IV-15, Folder 18)
  - Incoming, Canel, James, B. (Box IV-16, Folder 1)
  - Incoming, Canel, James, B. (Box IV-16, Folder 2)
  - Incoming, Canel, James, B. (Box IV-16, Folder 3)
  - Incoming, Canelas - Cano (Box IV-16, Folder 4)
  - Incoming, Caperton - Carienan (Box IV-16, Folder 5)
  - Incoming, Carl - Carnes (Box IV-16, Folder 6)
  - Incoming, Carney - Carter (Box IV-16, Folder 7)
  - Incoming, Cartwright - Catton (Box IV-16, Folder 8)
  - Incoming, Cavert - Chambers (Box IV-16, Folder 9)
  - Incoming, Chamorro - Chandler, Walter (Box IV-16, Folder 10)
  - Incoming, Chandler, William G. (Box IV-16, Folder 11)
  - Incoming, Chandler, William G (Box IV-16, Folder 12)
  - Incoming, Chandler, William G. - Chaplin (Box IV-16, Folder 13)
  - Incoming, Chappell - Charlet (Box IV-16, Folder 14)
  - Incoming, Charlton - Choate (Box IV-16, Folder 15)
  - Incoming, Chumley, Eflye (Box IV-16, Folder 16)
  - Incoming, Chumley, Efifye (Box IV-16, Folder 17)
  - Incoming, Chumley, Eflye (Box IV-16, Folder 18)
  - Incoming, Cinerama, Inc. - Clark (Box IV-16, Folder 19)
  - Incoming, Clarke - Clement (Box IV-16, Folder 20)
  - Incoming, Clements - Coe (Box IV-16, Folder 21)
  - Incoming, Coffin - Cole (Box IV-16, Folder 22)
  - Incoming,, Coley - Collinson (Box IV-17, Folder 1)
  - Incoming, Comer - Conlon (Box IV-17, Folder 2)
  - Incoming, Conn - Conwill (Box IV-17, Folder 3)
  - Incoming, Cook - Cool (Box IV-17, Folder 4)
  - Incoming, Cooper - Coosa (Box IV-17, Folder 5)
  - Incoming, Cope - Copely, James (Box IV-17, Folder 6)
  - Incoming, Copely, James (Box IV-17, Folder 7)
  - Incoming, Corbitt - Corral (Box IV-17, Folder 8)
  - Incoming, Corson - Cottrell (Box IV-17, Folder 9)
  - Incoming, Couch - Cowless, Mike (Box IV-17, Folder 10)
  - Incoming, Cowles, William H. (Box IV-17, Folder 11)
  - Incoming, Cowles, William H. (Box IV-17, Folder 12)
  - Incoming, Cowles, William H. (Box IV-17, Folder 13)
  - Incoming, Cox - Craig (Box IV-17, Folder 14)
  - Incoming, Crain - Cross (Box IV-17, Folder 15)
  - Incoming, Crow - Crump (Box IV-17, Folder 16)
  - Incoming, Crush - Curd (Box IV-17, Folder 17)
  - Incoming, Curran, Thomas B. (Box IV-17, Folder 18)
  - Incoming, Currey - Dale (Box IV-17, Folder 19)
  - Incoming, Dallman - Davenport (Box IV-17, Folder 20)
  - Incoming, David - Davis, E. C. (Box IV-18, Folder 1)
  - Incoming, Davis, E. L. - Davis, H. (Box IV-18, Folder 2)
  - Incoming, Davis, J. W. - Davis, W. L. (Box IV-18, Folder 3)
  - Incoming, Davison - Dealey, T. (Box IV-18, Folder 4)
  - Incoming, Dealey, T. (Box IV-18, Folder 5)
  - Incoming, Deans - Deering (Box IV-18, Folder 6)
  - Incoming, DePoe - Demmon (Box IV-18, Folder 7)
  - Incoming, Demson - Dent (Box IV-18, Folder 8)
  - Incoming, Depriest - Dickey (Box IV-18, Folder 9)
  - Incoming, Dickie - Dirksen (Box IV-18, Folder 10)
  - Incoming, Discala - Donald (Box IV-18, Folder 11)
  - Incoming, Dennelly - Doss (Box IV-18, Folder 12)
  - Incoming, Douglas, Beverly - Douglas, Mary (Box IV-18, Folder 13)
  - Incoming, Down - Dresslar (Box IV-18, Folder 14)
  - Incoming, Dreyfus, W. C. (Box IV-18, Folder 15)